imf.org 2004-06-06

# Privacy Policy - IMF Website

Terms and Conditions

Copyright and Permissions

IMF Disclosure/Transparency Policy

Access to IMF Archives

Contact Us

|   
|  |   
|  **Privacy Policy—www.imf.org**  
  
Last Updated: April 17, 2003 

This privacy policy statement applies to www.imf.org only. It does not apply to information collected and stored by a means other than the website. 

You will find the [International Financial Statistics Online](http://ifs.apdi.net/imf/logon.aspx) privacy policy statement at <http://ifs.apdi.net/imf/privacy.asp>.

**Privacy of Personal Information**

Out of respect for the privacy of its users, the IMF website (http://www.imf.org) refrains from obtaining personal information from users without their explicit consent. The IMF does not distribute, sell or rent any personal information collected via its website. This is also true for personal information (email address, postal address, etc.) sent to the website’s email addresses. The IMF does not send unsolicited emails to users of its site. The transmission of personal information entered via the site’s registration forms (e.g. [IMF Online Employment Application form](https://www.imf.org/external/np/adm/rec/db/index.htm), Annual and Spring Meetings registration form) is protected by security features.

 **Policy on Cookies**

The IMF website analyzes aggregate usage data to find out how often and when site content is requested. It does not use persistent cookies (text cookies) or session cookies for the purpose of tracking usage of its site. A persistent cookie, or text cookie, is a file that might contain user information. It is stored on a user’s computer. The IMF website uses session cookies (session cookies are not stored on a user’s computer) on two occasions: Two IMF online forums ( The Treatment of Nonperforming Loans in Macroeconomic Statistics and The Treatment of Pension Schemes in Macroeconomic Statistics) use session cookies when a user logs in and posts to a forum. Here session cookies are used to validate that the user is logged in to post to the forum. Other forums may be added to the site in the future.
